Daniel Ramirez Vega

Systems Engineer

Email: daniel.rave0903@gmail.com Address: San Francisco de Dos Ríos, San José, Costa Rica

Phone: 8849-0754 Date of birth: Mar 9, 2000 Nationality: Costa Rican

Social links, website: www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-ramírez-ve ga-61282422b

OBJECTIVE

Enter the labor market in a consolidated company that allows me to apply the knowledge that I have acquired during my studies, with the expectation of grow both professionally and personally. I am a Systems Engineer with experience in software development. Specialized in innovative and technological solutions, oriented to achievement of results and continuous improvement.

EXPERIENCE

San José, Costa Rica Jan 2019 - Feb 2022

San José, Costa Rica Mar 2023 - Feb 2024

Insurance Agent Assistant

Deal with customers, insurance payment functions, deal with insurance services providers, insurance expiration control and database data entry operation.

Jr Executive

GSI Corredora de Seguros

I was responsible for managing databases, generating reports based on database information, and performing mass notification distributions directly from the database.

EDUCATION

San José, Costa Rica Jan 2021 - Present

San José, Costa Rica Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

San José, Costa Rica Jan 2013 - Dec 2017

Systems Engineering

Universidad Fidélitas

I have currently completed 100% of the coursework, only pending the issuance of the degree.

Business Administration

Universidad de Costa Rica

Degree 50% completed, currently on hold.

Highschool

C.C.B / Liceo de Curridabat

Bilingual school

SKILLS

- Java
- JavaScript
- Python
- C#
- Spring Boot
- .NET
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL • SQL Server
- MySQL
- Software Testing · Good Leader
- Proactive
- Responsible
- Honest
- · I Learn Fast
- Good Principles

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced. My entire secondary education was at a bilingual school, combined with self-directed learning where I was able to develop my English knowledge.

REFERENCES

David Ortiz Castro.

Insurance Broker.

8380-7732.

Lic. Lucrecia Vega Román.

Educator.

8704-7707.

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

CCNAv7: Switching, Routing and Wireless Essentials

Scrum Fundamentals Certified

https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?

type=SFC&number=908163